goodmenproject.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - The Good Men Project

Privacy Policy  
Last Modified: May 25, 2018

Your privacy is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use, and share your personal information. This Privacy Policy governs all mobile websites and applications owned or operated by Good Men Media Inc. (“GMM” “we” or “us”), including The Good Men Project Web site (the “Site”) and any other applications, interactive features, widgets and resources offered by GMM through Internet Web sites, mobile devices or other platforms (collectively, the “Service”). By using the Service, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us. When you use the Service, you also consent to our Terms of Service.

1\. Questions and Opt Out.

If you would like to ask questions or provide comments regarding this Privacy Policy you may do so by sending us an e-mail at info@goodmenproject.com or by writing to us at GMM, Attn: Customer Service – Privacy, 87 N. Raymond Ave, #230, Pasadena, CA, 91103.

We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. 

If, after providing consent, you want to opt out of having your Personal Information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at info@goodmenproject.com or by writing to us at GMM, Attn: Customer Service – Privacy, 87 N. Raymond Ave, #230, Pasadena, CA, 91103. Please be sure to include your full name, your GMM username, the e-mail address you used to sign up with GMM and your mailing address and specifically state that you do not want your personal information shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

For residents of the European Union, we will not process your personal data without first obtaining your prior consent unless such processing is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations, is necessary to perform any contract we have with you, or is necessary for our legitimate interests.

2\. Updating Your Personal Information and Controlling Your Profile.

You may correct or update your personal information by emailing us at info@goodmenproject.com or writing us at 87 N. Raymond Ave, #230, Pasadena, CA, 91103.

3\. Information You Choose To Submit.

When you register to become a member of the Service, we collect certain information about you which may include such information as your name, e-mail address, gender, date of birth and credit card number or other payment information. We may also collect other personal information, including, without limitation, any personal information that you provide to us through the Services or in connection with any contests, sweepstakes and/or other promotions (collectively, “Personal Information”). When you post content through the Service, your username and other Personal Information may be included in the post.

4\. Information We Automatically Collect.

We automatically collect certain non-personal information to help us understand how our users use the Service (which we will refer to in this Privacy Policy, collectively, as “Usage Data”). Usage Data may include the IP address of the computer or server that you are using to access the Site, the IP address and/or the URL from the Web site you visited just before you visited our Site, the URL of the page you visit upon leaving the Site, if any, and the type of browser and operating system and device you are using. This anonymous usage information may be associated with your user name and profile, but we will not disclose the associated information to third parties.

In addition, we may use a technology called “cookies” and similar technologies. A cookie is a small file that identifies you as a unique user. We may use cookies to improve the quality of our Service and make the Service easier to use. We do this by storing information (for example, settings preferences) about a particular user session in cookies in order to provide you with a seamless experience during a particular session. Certain of our “Service Providers” (as defined below) may use cookies or similar technologies in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. If you choose to do so, you can configure your browser to delete existing cookies or disable cookies altogether. However, certain features of the Service may not work if you delete or disable cookies.

The Service does not respond to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of Personal Information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time. Visit www.donottrack.us to find out more about “do not track.”

We may work with third-party advertising companies that may use information about your use of the Service in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on the Service and on third party websites. From the Service, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as web beacons or pixel tags. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third party ad serving company may collect from you. These third-party advertising companies are required to comply with all applicable laws. For more information about ad cookies and companies that provide users the ability to “opt-out” of the collection of information from such cookies, please click here: .

5\. How We Use Information.

We may use your Personal Information to notify you of new product releases, to send service notifications, to customize the advertising and content you see, to improve our services, to conduct research, and to solicit your feedback and input about the Service. For contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions conducted on or through the Service, we use the Personal Information that you provide to communicate with you regarding such contest, sweepstakes or other promotion and in accordance with the applicable rules. If, in connection with any sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions, which might involve the sharing of your Personal Information with third-parties, we will obtain your consent for such disclosure.

6\. How We Share Your Information.

Other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, except for aggregate information that we may share with third parties in a manner that does not link such information to any individual, we will not share your Personal Information with third parties, unless you have given us permission to do so.

We may sometimes use other businesses (“Service Providers”) to perform certain services for us, e.g., to provide certain services on our behalf, such as payment processing, hosting and maintenance, data storage and management services, production and fulfillment, and marketing and promotions. We provide our Service Providers with the information reasonably necessary for them to perform the services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

We may disclose aggregate Usage Data in order to (a) describe the use of the Service to our existing or potential business partners, GMMs, advertisers, investors or other third parties; (b) comply with laws, regulations, court orders or subpoenas or in response to a government request; or (c) protect or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will not involve the disclosure of Personal Information nor personally identify you or any other users of the Service.

We reserve the right to make all of the following information about you available to all other users of the Service: (a) any information you choose to include in your Service profile; (b) any photos or other personal media content you submit to us or that you have shared through the Service; and (c) your GMM username.

7\. Other Authorized Disclosures.

Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, you understand and agree that GMM may access, preserve, and disclose any information we have collected about you or that you have submitted: (a) in response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish, protect or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (b) to protect the rights and property of GMM, its affiliates or the public; (c) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, copyright violations, trademark violations or other violations of the personal or intellectual property rights of others or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person; (d) to our corporate affiliates, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with GMM (in which case we will require such entities to honor this Privacy Policy); and (e) if GMM is acquired by or merged with another entity or in connection with a sale of our assets. In addition, GMM may forward any copyright infringement Notification, Counter Notification (as each of those terms is defined in the Terms of Service) or trademark infringement notice that you submit pursuant to GMM’s Terms of Service, and any related communications, to third parties.

8\. Public Areas.

Your use of areas of the Service that are intended for interaction with other users may reveal your username and may allow you to publish certain personal information about you. By choosing to use these areas, you understand and agree that anyone with access to those areas may access and forward any information about you that is contained in or that you post to those areas. As with any social networking service, you should use care when disclosing your personal information to strangers.

9\. Links to Other Sites.

The Service may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked websites may be different from our Privacy Policy. You access such linked websites at your own risk. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any such linked website you visit to understand that website’s collection, storage and use of your information.

10\. Security.

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information in an effort to protect information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. We also require our Service Providers to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we share with them. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect Personal Information, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the Service, and you do so at your own risk.

11\. Children’s Privacy Statement.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen (13), we will delete such information from our records. Because we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13), we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

12\. Rights of European Union Residents

For residents of the European Union, the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) requires that GMM take particular measures to protect the personal data of European residents. If there is any conflict between this policy and the GDPR, the GDPR principles shall govern with respect to residents of the European Union.

Under the GDPR, you have the right to request a copy of your personal data stored at GMM (Article 15 GDPR). You also have the right to request corrections (Article 16 GDPR), deletion (Article 17 GDPR) or restriction (Article 18 GDPR) of your personal data stored at GMM.

You may send your requests for access, correction, deletion or restriction to the privacy officer of GMM at lisa@goodmenproject.com.

If a European resident is dissatisfied with the handling of your personal data by GMM, you have the right to object to processing of your personal data at any time (Article 21 GDPR). You may send your concerns or objections about the processing of your personal data to lisa@goodmenproject.com. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

13\. Non-European Residents.

Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we may process and store all information in the United States. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Service, you agree that the collection, use, transfer and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.

14\. Changes.

GMM may, in its sole and absolute discretion, change this Privacy Policy from time to time. All changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective when posted, and we will provide notification of such changes to you via the Service or contact information you may have provided to GMM upon registration. In order to continue using the Service following any changes to the Privacy Policy of which we notify you, you must agree to be bound by such changes. If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Service.

Effective date: January 1, 2017.
